http://www.ngaming.co.uk/misc/privacy.html

Privacy Statement for nGaming(ngaming.co.uk)Starsol.co.uk has created this privacy statement in order demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for nGaming (ngaming.co.uk).Information Automatically LoggedThis site uses your I.P. address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site.nGaming records the browser type to monitor market penetration of various web browsers so we can better determine the internet technologies we may utilize in the design of our pages.nGaming uses page referrer data - that is, information about the page that linked you to this page - to determine to what extent our page is referenced by other resources on the internet.This data may be used to preserve the integrity of our computing resources.Personal InformationnGaming collects personal information such as your specified nGaming username and e-mail address that are submitted using our online forms.The information submitted is used to improve the content of our website. Your email address is not published in any form. Your specified username may accompany any content you submit to the nGaming website and also appear elsewhere on the nGaming website.We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes beyond those stated in this privacy statement.Links to External SitesnGaming contains links to external websites which are not operated by or affiliated with Starsol.co.uk. Starsol.co.uk is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.CookiesTo enable preferences regarding layout and targeting content for users country, and to allow registered members of nGaming to log in to use members only features of nGaming, cookies may be placed on the computers of visitors to nGaming.Only ngaming.co.uk has access to these cookies.These cookies are saved until ten years from the time of visit. Registered member password cookies are encrypted using the MD5 message-digest algorithm.SecuritynGaming has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, nGaming has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers. Third Party CookiesIn the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser.Contact InformationIf you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact an administrator.
